# Michael Emborsky

3536 Shell Quarry Dr • Wilmington, NC 28412 • (716) – 870 – 7734 • michaelemborsky@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Michael Emborsky is a globally minded individual, and through a range of diverse experiences living overseas, has developed considerably the ability to be adaptive, and to connect with other cultures. Due to this quality and due to a high degree of self-motivation, Michael is a highly reliable individual ready and willing to act as an intelligent and loyal team member, contributing to a productive work environment.

#### **Key Strengths**

- Work Ethic and Detail Oriented
  - o Fully committed to a task until completed to a high degree.
  - Detail focused to ensure quality product.
- Well Organized
  - o Strong time-management and organizational abilities
- Flexible and Impactful Team Member
  - o Experience and flexibility with working with a great variety of cultures and people.

#### Software and Programming Languages

- Strong understanding of Python and Java
- Adept at audio production software including FL Studio and Pro Tools
- Adept at visual production software including Photoshop, Illustrator, and After Effects
- Significant understanding and experience with web-based languages, specifically HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Experience with Swift, C++, F#, SML, Prolog

#### Links

- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-emborsky-670477256
- GitHub <a href="https://github.com/mjemborsky">https://github.com/mjemborsky</a>
- Personal Website <a href="https://mjemborsky.com">https://mjemborsky.com</a>

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Computer Science, concentration in Digital Arts** – (2020 – Present)

(Graduation: Fall 2023)

University of North Carolina, Wilmington

Associate of Science – (2020)

Cape Fear Community College

#### **2 Year International Baccalaureate Diploma – (2014 – 2016)**

American Community School of Abu Dhabi, Abu Dhabi, U.A.E

### CURRENT AND PAST PROJECTS

# SoundScape

Platform: Windows, Mac Application Languages: C++

(In Progress)
A desktop application for Mac and
Windows that allows for the full
customization of a user's sound
elements/inputs.

## myCloset

Platform: iOS Application Languages: C++

An iOS application that allows for a user to upload, save, and create collages of clothing items and share them with their followers.

### **Lotus State Website**

Platform: Website Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

A live website for my Artist profile, Lotus State. Features immersive animations produced with Javascript, SVGs and queries.

# **Budget Calculator**

Platform: Java Application Languages: C++

An application developed with Java that assists the user in planning and creating a personal or business budget.

#### PAST WORK EXPERIENCE

**The Getaway Cafe** – Shift Leader

(Summer 2021 – Present)

Independence Mall, Wilmington, NC

- Interact with customers to provide a personable experience.
- Handle money and operate a cash register.
- Maintain organization and appearance in the stockroom and on the floor.

**Vans** – Sales Associate

(Summer 2021 – Present)

Independence Mall, Wilmington, NC

- Interact with customers to provide a personable experience.
- Handle money and operate a cash register.
- Maintain organization and appearance in the stockroom and on the floor.